Select Page

Privacy Policy
==============

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from [www.weaberlumber.com](https://www.weaberlumber.com/).

1. **Personal Information We Collect:**
    * When you visit our Website, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Website, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to our Website, and information about how you interact with our Website. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information”.
    * We collect Device Information using the following technologies:
        1. “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.
        2. “Log files” track actions occurring on the Website, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.
        3. “Web beacons”, “tags”, and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Website.
    * Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through our Website, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit card numbers, email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information”.
    * When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.
2. **How Do We Use Your Personal Information?**
    * We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Website (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to:
        1. Communicate with you;
        2. Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and
        3. When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.
    * We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Website (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Website, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).
3. **Sharing Your Personal Information:**
    * We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above.
        1. We use WooCommerce to power our online store. You can read more about how WooCommerce uses your Personal Information here: https://woo.com/
        2. We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Website. You can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://policies.google.com
    * We may share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.
    * We may also share your information in the event of a business transaction, such as a merger, acquisition, or sale of assets.
4. **Behavioral Advertising:**
    * We use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.
    * You can opt out of targeted advertising by using the links below:
        1. Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads
        2. Google: https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous
        3. Bing:https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads
    * Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: http://optout.aboutads.info/.
5. **Marketing Communications:** \[INSERT IF APPLICABLE\].
6. **Do Not Track:** Please note that we do not alter our Website’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.
7. **Data Retention:** We will retain your Personal Information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Policy, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law. We will securely dispose of or de-identify personal information when it is no longer needed.
8. **Security:**
    * When you place orders on our Website or through our mobile applications, all of your order information, including your credit card number and delivery address, is transmitted through the Internet using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. SSL technology causes your browser to encrypt your order information before transmitting it to our secure server. SSL technology, an industry standard, is designed to prevent someone other than operators of our websites from capturing and viewing your personal information.
    * While we use industry standard means to protect our websites and your information, the Internet is not 100% secure. The measures we use are appropriate for the type of information we collect. We cannot promise that your use of our websites or mobile applications will be completely safe. We encourage you to use caution when using the Internet. Online access to your personal information is protected with a password you select. We strongly recommend that you do not share your password and that you use unique passwords for all of your online accounts.
9. **Third-Party Websites and Services:** The Website may contain links to third-party websites or services that are not owned or controlled by us. This Policy does not apply to those third-party platforms. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of those platforms before providing any personal information.
10. **Children’s Privacy:** Our Website and device applications are not created for children. To our knowledge, we neither collect online information from, nor sell nor share information regarding children under 18. If you are a parent or guardian and think we have information about your child, please contact us at 1-800-745-9663 or [customerservice@weaber.com](mailto:customerservice@weaber.com). To learn more about how to protect your child online, visit the FTC’s www.OnGuardOnline.gov. You may also want to read the helpful information about children and privacy that the FTC provides on the Protecting Your Child’s Privacy Online page.
11. **Policy Updates:** We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.
12. **Contact Us**: For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us at 1-800-745-9663 or [customerservice@weaber.com](mailto:customerservice@weaber.com).

#### Company Information

#### Products

#### Contact

### ingrained with innovation®

© Copyright 2018 - 2024 Weaber

.

Español »
